<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Luis G. Villegas</title><link>https://luisguve.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Luis G. Villegas</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 15:30:57 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://luisguve.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Strapi Plugin Ratings</title><link>https://luisguve.github.io/plugins/strapi-plugin-ratings/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 15:30:57 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://luisguve.github.io/plugins/strapi-plugin-ratings/</guid><description>Ratings is a Strapi plugin that allows your users to post reviews.
Enable and manage user reviews for your content very easily!
Requirements You should have installed an instance of Strapi v4.x.x
Installation Run the following command in your project root:
npm install strapi-plugin-ratings Then, rebuild the admin dashboard using the following command
npm run build Configurarion For your frontend to have access to the API, enable the following permissions for Ratings from Users &amp;amp; Permissions Plugin on your project settings:</description></item><item><title>How To Enable And Manage Comments In Your Strapi Application</title><link>https://luisguve.github.io/tutorials/how-to-enable-and-manage-comments-in-your-strapi-application/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 08:48:34 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://luisguve.github.io/tutorials/how-to-enable-and-manage-comments-in-your-strapi-application/</guid><description>Outline Introduction Prerequisites What is Strapi Comment Manager? Installation Configuration Display comments on the frontend Installation of Strapi Comments Client Usage of Strapi Comments Client Plugin settings Manage comments Full source code of the frontend Conclusion Introduction A comment system comes in very handy for pretty much any kind of website. In the JAMstack ecosystem, while it&amp;rsquo;s ok to rely on third party solutions hosted on their own platform such as Disqus to enable comments, you usually want to keep your content and all the stuff related to it in the same admin dashboard.</description></item><item><title>Strapi Plugin Comment Manager</title><link>https://luisguve.github.io/plugins/strapi-plugin-comment-manager/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 08:35:57 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://luisguve.github.io/plugins/strapi-plugin-comment-manager/</guid><description>Comment Manager is a Strapi plugin to allow your users to post comments.
With this plugin you can enable and manage comments for your content very easily!
Requirements You should have installed an instance of Strapi v4.x.x
Installation Run the following command in your project root:
npm install strapi-plugin-comment-manager Configurarion For your frontend to have access to the API, enable the following permissions for Comment Manager from Users &amp;amp; Permissions Plugin on your project settings:</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://luisguve.github.io/pages/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://luisguve.github.io/pages/about/</guid><description>This is my portfolio, where you will find a lot of content related to Strapi, the best headless CMS out there.
Here you will find tutorials on how to install &amp;amp; use my plugins, both in the Strapi application and the frontend through their API.
Follow @luisguve</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://luisguve.github.io/pages/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://luisguve.github.io/pages/contact/</guid><description>You can reach me out at my email: luisguveal@gmail.com</description></item></channel></rss>